I am feeling good about ICICI Lombard for earning Rs 10.
Here we have seen that as per the
calculations, there was a big rally earlier,
after that there was a correction in the stock
from 2250 to
2050-2080. From there, the stock has again
created a good momentum in the last three days and is regaining its strength. At the same time, the
stock has come above its 20-day
external moving average
and is standing strong. If we
look at the weekly chart, it is completely an up
trending chart after June 2024 and just
this last week there was a retest of
important moving averages. I
feel that here ICICI Lombard should be taken
at lower levels or current price or on a small
dip. Stop loss of 2140
and targets of 2220 to 2250 are
visible here. If it sustains above 2250, then it will be
up.  If side YP
can open then buy it for short term, if the
stock goes above 2250 then do not rush to
sell and keep training
for the higher side, it is absolutely right, so this is the
advice for you to buy ICICI Lombard for Rs 10, right now the
target is in front of you from Sudish Sahab,
240 more are seen coming towards 2250